Hi, folks, and welcome to section 3 for this tutorial.
So here, this section is actually very simple.
We do only verification, and we almost will not do any new configuration.
So the first task is to ensure that PHP and Apache inside the container are running the latest version.
So, first here, we need to log into the container.
Okay, and then to check for the PHP latest version, we just type PHP-P.
Okay, and it's very simple. As you can see here, it is version 8.5.0, which is the latest stable version.
Okay, and the same applies here for the Apache, but we will type Apache to CTL.
Apache to CTL-V. Okay, it will show to us that we have the latest also Apache server version 2.4.65.
So, we have done the modifications that we have the latest Apache and PHP version.
For MySQL, the comment is a little bit lengthy.
Okay, we have actually two methods.
This method will enter it by simply, we will not type Docker-PHP, but of course MySQL, and we'd execute the comment of MySQL, but we will type the issue, which mean we'll log in with the root user.
And then we need to dash E and select version, so that the comment is extended to select version.
Okay, sorry, there is a miss typo.
There is a miss typo here. Okay, I just sorry, missed the quotation.
This is very important to set the double quotation.
Okay, and of course we need first to exit the Docker to execute this comment from the host itself.
So, we will enter not the user password, but the root password.
So, we need to remember it.
Okay, you need to take care of the password.
If you type it correctly, you will have access denied.
So, that's why the first time I got access denied, but when I enter it the second time, it shows me that I got the version 9.50.
So, this is the hard implementation for it.
If you want a simpler implementation, you can just type this comment.
Okay, Docker, exit, dash E, my MySQL, but you will select my SQL dash dash version.
Okay, take care to type it correctly.
You need to type my SQL, not my SQL D.
Because if you type my SQL D, it will cause many problems and you do not execute success.
Okay, as you can see here, it shows to us that we have MySQL, also 9.50.
Okay, so we have finished also this part and we finished section 3.
Section 3 is very, very easy.
So here.